Hello!
We're back.
In this segment, we're going to tackle choosing a voice.
Some people think do you choose the character first and then the voice, or the voice and then the character.
It's up to you.
In this segment, we're going to just handle how to choose a voice.
There's very many ways to do it.
You can pick it through an accent.
Take for instance a British accent.
Pass me the mohee mohee.
You can do it like a sailor.
You can do you a higher pitch.
I want to talk like this or I want to talk like that with a lower pitch.
You can adjust the rate.
You can talk really fast.
Maybe you want to talk this fast or you can talk very slowly and methodically as a puppet.
Maybe you want to throw some other elements all together like a lisp.
Maybe he talks like this.
He can't say certain letters, so he lisps a little bit.
Either way you're going to want to practice.
Like we mentioned, use your tools, record it, listen to the voice, and test it out on some of your friends.
Are they getting good response?
Do they like your voice?
Is your character's voice engaging?
Is it something that you want to carry with you and go through many routines with?